[Dail] You have no idea
how badly I've wanted to come in here.
I've wanted to be
in this Dining Room so bad.
Dail and I've never been
to the Main Hall before.
-[♪ amusing music playing]
-So this is the Main Hall.
Let's do a toast.
[Ddolddol] Good work.
-[Pani Bottle] Ah...
-[slurping loudly, exclaims]
[slurping loudly]
Are you going to bed, Horseking?
Are you going to sleep?
-I don't know.
-Okay.
Good night.
-See you tomorrow.
-[Horseking] Good night.
AWKWARD RESPONSE FROM OTHERS
[Ddolddol] I don't think
we're exactly welcome.
-Huh?
-I don't think we're exactly welcome.
Even better.
This is exactly what I wanted.
They reacted like, "There are
more survivors than I expected."
Like, "Get a load of these punks."
I love it.
Let's crush them all.
When we returned to the house,
there wasn't a single person who said,
"I'm glad you guys are back.
Welcome back."
EARLIER IN THE MAIN HALL
[Pani Bottle groans] My back hurts.
STRANGE TENSE MOOD IN THE MAIN HALL
[Ddolddol] I got the feeling
they were thinking,
"They actually made it back alive."
That actually gave me
even more motivation.
The three of us have such a strong bond
that whenever we say something,
it carries a lot of weight.
I think the entire dynamic will change.
Honestly, we had amazing teamwork.
Today went really well.
But I think
we were too brutal when we took them out.
-What did you do?
-They couldn't do a thing.
It wasn't because it was Jieun.
We would've taken out anyone.
[Ddolddol] The three of us were already
on the same side.
[Dail] It was basically like this.
Whoever ended up there
would never get out.
You might as well have brought
someone strong in,
because nobody could beat us.
[Ddolddol] I think going down to prison
was a good thing
because I found people
who trusted me and had my back.
The prison team came back
with such a strong bond.
They were almost like a family.
It was more than an alliance.
Our concern is that the Seeker Vote
is coming up tomorrow.
[Pani Bottle] Let's talk about that later.
I was going to bring it up anyway.
[Jaegyun] You can talk
about it now. It's fine.
Just in case.
[Eunsil] Let's go.
[Sanghyun] I think
they're going to talk about me.
[Junseo] That you're the Seeker?
[Sanghyun] Ddolddol
keeps suspecting me so much.
I'm starting to get a little angry.
Did he leave?
Yeah. So...
What was Sanghyun's last name?
-Youn Sanghyun.
-Youn Sanghyun?
-I'm 97 to 99% sure it's him.
-[Pani Bottle] I know.
I've barely spoken to him,
but isn't he clearly winning right now?
Yes.
He's dominating.
-[Ddolddol] He has 120 million won.
-Right.
It's about time someone kept him in check.
That's what we agreed among ourselves.
I heard he found a hidden mission
that wasn't even in the original rules.
Are you really taking his word for it?
Because of that,
we're a little suspicious of him.
But I'm not sure if the others
feel the same way.
[Dail] Of all people, the one in first?
If you're on the fence,
maybe you should team up with us
-and split that group up.
-[Ddolddol] Trust my gut on this.
Even if Sanghyun isn't the Seeker,
there's a lot to gain.
Wouldn't it be good to prove his alibi
if he doesn't want people to suspect him?
[Pani Bottle] We came back from prison,
and we're small in number.
I thought we needed to bring
more people onto our side.
I suspect Sanghyun is the Seeker.
If he's not, no big deal.
It's because he's so good
and dominating the game.
I told them we need to keep
the strong player in check.
Give it some thought. We're not saying
we have to stick together forever.
Later, we'll split up anyway.
But for now, I think we need
to keep the former cops in check.
So yeah, we did talk about that
among ourselves too.
We did talk about it.
THE PRISON ALLIANCE SUGGESTS
JOINING FORCES WITH THEM
[ZZONE] The prison alliance
seems really strong.
[Jimin] Their bond is no joke.
The prison team is too intimidating.
[ZZONE] They're definitely intimidating.
Up until now,
the alliances have always been
about teaming up with people
who could benefit you in each match.
But the prison crew is insane.
They're like, "We're going to eliminate
everyone here."
But they have four people over there.
[ZZONE] It's three now since Sujin's gone.
-[Jimin] Right.
-Joonsu is pretty close with them too.
He'll probably side with whoever gives him
the best advantage.
Jaegyun is close with them.
To break them apart,
we need to send them back to prison.
[Jimin] From what I heard from the people
who survived prison,
it felt like they teamed up
and eliminated Jieun.
It felt like it'd naturally turn
into a battle
between the mansion group
and the prison members.
I'm not sure what will happen
going forward.
[crow cawing]
[Eunsil] It feels like
we've been here forever,
but we've only done the second Main Match.
Only two have been eliminated.
We need to eliminate them all quickly,
-starting with the prison family.
-[♪ intriguing music playing]
[Jimin] Right?
[Eunsil] Yeah!
Can't we just eliminate Pani Bottle again?
We can just send him home
and keep things simple.
Individual competitions...
I bet there will be
more team-based games ahead.
So definitely,
I think we'll need to have
alliances going forward.
Yeah, if an alliance agrees
to take one person out,
-in that case...
-For sure.
...they can get that person
eliminated for sure.
[mic feedback]
[host] Please gather in the Main Hall.
We will now begin the Seeker Vote.
Before the vote, we will reveal whether
the Seeker succeeded in their mission.
In the previous Main Match,
"Time Between Dogs and Wolves"...
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
the Seeker failed.
-Nice!
-[♪ upbeat music playing]
Great.
[Eunsil] I was surprised
that the Seeker failed the mission.
[Horseking] It just felt great
to hear the Seeker failed.
You ended up failing. You failed.
[host] Since the Seeker failed
their mission,
we will now reveal
what the failed mission was.
This is a huge penalty.
[host] "Get incorrectly tagged
by two players of your choice."
[Horseking] "Get incorrectly tagged"?
Ah, so that's what the missions are like.
Their goal was to get incorrectly tagged.
But they failed that?
How do you even fail that?
I don't know since I didn't play the game,
but is that hard to pull off?
-It's easy.
-Honestly, I think it's easy.
-It seems so easy.
-It's easy?
Because all you have to do
is get tagged by everyone.
If the Seeker gets tagged
by everyone else while they're a Hunter,
they've completed the mission.
Then, shouldn't we find out
who was trying to get tagged
-on purpose?
-That's the most likely approach.
It's a separate mission
that has nothing to do
with winning or losing.
Even if they'd pulled it off,
it would've been
very difficult for us to know.
We probably would've never known.
[♪ tense music playing]
It says, "if the Seeker
fails their mission," right?
Then, we can rule out
two people as suspects.
"The Seeker cannot select themselves."
If they fail, the two people they pick
are revealed and ruled out.
That's right.
Then, these two will have a lot of clues.
The two selected players really need to
remember who they tagged yesterday.
-Exactly.
-Yeah.
[host] We will now reveal the two players
selected by the Seeker for their mission.
The players chosen by the Seeker are...
Hwang Jaegyun
and Shin Jieun.
Excluding Hwang Jaegyun and Shin Jieun,
the Seeker candidates
are among the 10 other players.
The Seeker selected two players
other than themselves,
so that rules out
Jieun and Jaegyun as suspects.
-We're cleared. I'm not the Seeker.
-It's 0%.
[Ddolddol] And I can't be the Seeker
since I already went to prison.
[Dail] The Seeker made the right choice.
Jaegyun was obviously
not the Seeker from the start.
[Dail chuckles]
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[Eunsil] So here's the thing.
"Get incorrectly tagged
by two players of your choice."
Right, the Seeker failed that mission.
But I never tagged anyone incorrectly.
[Dail] Isn't that possible?
-Then, isn't it a prison member?
-What?
-Isn't it a prison member?
-[Jaegyun] It is.
-Right?
-[Jaegyun] It could be
-among the players from prison.
-[Eunsil] They couldn't play at all.
Even if you're unable to participate
in the Main Match,
-it counts as a failure.
-It's a failure.
Since they failed,
everyone except Ddolddol,
-like Dail and Pani Bottle...
-[Eunsil] They're included.
-...are included again.
-[Eunsil] Right.
-[indistinct chatter]
-Yes, again.
Then, Yang Dail...
[Ddolddol] One thing is clear.
The prison members
couldn't participate anyway.
And my alibi
from the first Seeker Vote was proven.
-Us three should be ruled out.
-The thing is...
According to the Seeker rules,
not participating in the Main Match
also counts as a mission failure.
Ah...
[Jaegyun] It's highlighted as a key detail
at the very bottom.
If the mission was a success,
all prison members would've been cleared,
because they couldn't participate.
But at the end of the day,
no matter how much we talk about this,
-we're the only ones who know.
-[Jaegyun] Right.
But from our perspective,
we can't completely rule out
the prison members,
even if it's only 1% or 2% possible.
-The possibility isn't zero.
-Exactly.
-But it's extremely unlikely.
-[Jaegyun] Right.
Do we really need to consider that?
[Jaegyun] The chances are very slim.
[Ddolddol] The Seeker? Seriously?
I was so annoyed.
I can't stand how annoying the Seeker is.
I bet you heard this and narrowed it down.
Does everyone have one in mind?
I'm a little confused.
But it definitely narrowed down, right?
She lost in the game, but she was
the one who really came at me.
ZZONE? Right, I was pretty surprised too.
[Horseking] It'd make sense
if she went after us as a Hunter,
but she did it when she was a Dog.
It wasn't a wrong tag.
[Jaegyun] That'd be a weird strategy.
When I saw the Seeker's mission,
[Sanghyun] I thought we could
narrow things down a little.
Considering the mission
was to get incorrectly tagged,
it should be someone
who was around Jaegyun and Jieun a lot.
If we rule people out,
it has to be someone
who challenged Jaegyun
or got tagged by him.
In the first round,
those who did that were
these two, ZZONE and Joonsu.
Someone who was aggressive
when they were a Hunter in Round 1
might have held back in Round 2
due to too many negative points.
[ZZONE] Jimin got tagged by eight people.
In Round 1?
[ZZONE] She got tagged by eight people
when she was a Hunter.
Everyone except Jaegyun tagged her.
[Jimin screams]
No, wait a minute.
JIMIN WAS TAGGED MORE THAN ANYONE ELSE
-No, hold on! [pants]
-[ZZONE] Let's go.
Even if she was a Hunter,
she walked around so freely.
[Jimin] Well, look at this. Of all people,
ZZONE is coming after me.
No, I didn't tag Jimin.
-I never got tagged by Horseking.
-[Jaegyun] Not me.
So when Jimin was a Hunter,
her strategy wasn't to tag others.
It was to get tagged to lower our scores.
-I hid the whole time aside from that.
-[Jaegyun] Yeah.
Did either Jaegyun
or Jieun incorrectly tag you?
-[ZZONE] Jieun did.
-I didn't tag Jimin.
-I didn't tag her.
But there is this possibility
if I may cautiously suggest this.
There's a chance the Seeker
picked Jaegyun and Jieun
to fail the mission intentionally.
-You have a point.
-Because if I were the Seeker,
-I wouldn't want to clear every mission.
-[♪ serious music playing]
That would make me
-look especially suspicious.
-[ZZONE] Right.
With that in mind, if you win
and clear the Seeker mission too,
that will look too obvious.
So you'd have to give one up.
But revealing two people like that
confirms they're not the Seeker.
Isn't ruling out two people
a huge risk for the Seeker?
The Seeker may have decided
to give up on the mission from the start.
They could've considered that
and picked the two people
who'd be hurt the least by revealing...
[Ddolddol] They could've revealed people
they were okay with revealing.
Then, we can't rule anyone out.
They could be someone who didn't try
or someone who genuinely tried
and just failed.
That could apply to any of us.
[Ddolddol] Right, so it's hard to tell.
The Seeker is too good at this game.
That's when I realized,
"This Seeker is on another level."
As for the prison members,
Pani Bottle and Yang Dail,
there's no reason
to rule them out as suspects.
If anything, this gives us a reason
to suspect them even more.
Let's go upstairs and talk.
There's no point in listening to them.
Just for a minute.
THE PRISON ALLIANCE STEPS AWAY
Even if we hear about yesterday,
we won't really know what happened.
Ddolddol and I were constantly
suspicious of Sanghyun.
Every single thing Sanghyun did
seemed really suspicious to me.
Just check out
where he's standing right now.
He's in the perfect spot to keep an eye
on everyone's movements.
If I were the Seeker, I'd stand there
to monitor where everyone was going.
Since yesterday, I've noticed
he gets really anxious
when people start splitting up.
I ended up in prison last time
because my political play failed.
This time, I really need to
handle the politics carefully
and get the votes I need.
[Pani Bottle] Joonsu.
Come here for a second.
[Sanghyun] I was like, "Do they have
something to discuss privately?"
[Dail] Jaegyun.
[ZZONE] So
they're definitely not the Seeker.
I should go talk to the people upstairs.
THE GROUP WHO GATHERED LAST NIGHT
[Sanghyun] I couldn't forget the look
in Ddolddol's eyes.
It seemed like people were divided.
Are we sticking with the plan
or thinking a bit more?
[Ddolddol] I don't think
we need to think more.
Without thinking, the prison team
-will stick with it.
-[Dail] Jaegyun.
I guarantee you.
-I felt it too just now.
-Just now?
I went from 99% to 99.9%.
[Junseo] They might have failed.
The prison team too...
But there are more of them.
[Sanghyun] But the prison team...
-They didn't play the game.
-[Junseo] Two were revealed here.
SANGHYUN COMES
TO WHERE THE PRISON MEMBERS ARE
[Sanghyun] Who could it be from prison?
Their instincts are terrible.
THE PRISON ALLIANCE LEAVES RIGHT AWAY
[sighs]
-[Junseo] It's the obvious choice.
-[Sanghyun] Yeah, honestly.
Let's check first.
I have no doubt.
[Ddolddol] Trust the trend.
[Dail] I want you to trust us
on this, ZZONE.
[ZZONE] For the vote?
[Dail] Let's at least check.
[ZZONE] Because it would clear two people
as not being the Seeker?
[Sanghyun] Am I under suspicion right now?
-[ZZONE] What?
-Am I under suspicion?
Hell yeah, you are.
-Me?
-[ZZONE] Yeah.
-Why?
-Who is?
[ZZONE] The prison team.
The prison team?
[Sanghyun] Why?
I'm not sure why exactly,
but let's find out together.
-[sighs]
-[ZZONE chuckles]
[Sanghyun] I realized that opinions
created by gaslighting
can turn into something powerful
and scary when they pile up.
[Junseo] Pani Bottle,
who seems the most suspicious to you?
[Pani Bottle] I voted based on
what I believed was right.
-You voted?
-Yes, I did.
[Sanghyun] So the prison team
is just voting
regardless of what we discussed
in the Main Match?
What we've heard
hasn't really convinced us.
We're not sure.
[Sanghyun] You wouldn't know
what was a fact?
Exactly. Even after hearing it,
we don't get it.
I don't know the rulebook.
I haven't read it.
[Sanghyun] In the Main Match,
their mission failed.
SANGHYUN MAKES HIS CASE
So there are people
we can narrow down from this.
[Ddolddol] I didn't really listen to him.
I'm sure he's nervous.
[Sanghyun] Did you have to vote
so quickly?
I believe the Seeker
will be caught eventually.
-They'll be caught at some point.
-They have a completely different mindset.
They're extremely stubborn.
They're so stubborn
that it's impossible to convince them.
If they're cleared, then good.
-If not, it gets complicated.
-Yeah.
[Pani Bottle] We can't force anyone.
All we can do is try to persuade others
or make our case.
We can't blame others
for not doing what we wanted.
I didn't really have anything else to say.
-Can I ask you something?
-[Horseking] What?
[Sanghyun] Do you still suspect me?
To be honest,
it's not even about suspicion.
-[Sanghyun] Okay.
-It's based on the circumstances.
[Sanghyun] Am I included in that?
Of course.
-From the start...
-[Sanghyun] But why?
I just don't get it.
Their mission failed in the Main Match.
I never even showed you my back.
That's true. So, we were saying...
[Sanghyun] And I avoided Jieun
the whole time.
SANGHYUN GETS WORKED UP
If I were the Seeker, I'd just get tagged.
Why bother tagging her too?
[Horseking] She did suddenly
come after you.
Exactly. That's why I think...
You come with me.
[Sanghyun] I'm upset.
[Eunsil] Why?
[Sanghyun] Because of the prison team.
[Eunsil] They all pinned it on you.
[Sanghyun] I mean,
I don't care if they suspect me.
But we can figure things out
based on the clues.
[Eunsil] The prison team seems
dead set on voting you out.
[Sanghyun] I know.
[smacks lips, sighs]
[Sanghyun] Everyone's been suspecting me
as the Seeker
ever since day one,
so I was mentally exhausted.
I no longer had the chance
to convince people anymore.
THE VOTES ARE LEANING TOWARD SANGHYUN
[sighs wearily]
PLAYERS CAST THEIR VOTES RIGHT AWAY
Hello.
Please vote for who you think
is the Seeker.
SEEKER VOTE
YOUN SANGHYUN
[Sanghyun] Did Jimin vote?
-[Jimin] Sanghyun.
-[Sanghyun] Yeah? Come here.
To be honest, I'm a little mad.
[Jimin] Why?
[Sanghyun] We could've figured things out.
-We could've narrowed it down.
-[Jimin] Right.
[Sanghyun] I was so frustrated.
I thought you played
an amazing game yesterday.
I know you're frustrated and upset,
but it's because you played so well.
And if you're actually the Seeker,
then you played it really well.
[Sanghyun] I'm really losing my cool.
[sighs] Seriously.
[host] Voting has ended.
Please gather in the Main Hall.
[Pani Bottle sighs heavily]
[Dail] I was 100% sure it was Sanghyun,
so I just watched his reaction.
I was thinking to myself,
"It's you, isn't it?" [laughs]
[Ddolddol] I'm 99% sure
it's Youn Sanghyun.
[host] Here is the result.
The player who received the most votes...
is Youn Sanghyun.
[sighs]
[Ddolddol] This time,
I succeeded in playing politics.
[host] Your attempt to catch the Seeker...
has failed.
[Sanghyun] I kept saying it wasn't me.
[host] Due to failure
to capture the Seeker,
we will reveal the elimination candidate
chosen by the Seeker.
The elimination candidate
chosen by the Seeker...
is Youn Sanghyun.
[players] What?
[Joonsu] Again?
What?
-What?
-[Joonsu] Again?
[Jaegyun exclaims]
[Eunsil] The Seeker had already voted,
knowing Sanghyun
would be up for the Seeker Vote.
Seriously, who is it?
The Seeker is really smart.
[Ddolddol] I truly felt so bad.
I thought maybe I should beg
for forgiveness.
I'm so sorry.
[host] Youn Sanghyun,
please leave the area immediately.
Sanghyun. [laughs]
I'll come visit you.
[♪ suspenseful string music playing]
[Sanghyun] Ah...
Honestly, I'm really mad
at the other players.
[fake whimpering]
Ah, unbelievable.
[sighs]
They didn't vote
based on their own judgment
and followed the crowd instead.
I just don't get it.
I just want to beat them all.
[Pani Bottle] By the way... [sighs]
-I'm a little shocked.
-[Dail] It is shocking.
[Jaegyun sighs] I'm so confused.
So the Seeker is among us right now.
No way, no way.
[Eunsil] I'm so annoyed.
[Horseking sighs] What's going on?
We can't help but think now
the Seeker could be among the prison team.
That's on the table now.
I think we need
to start reconsidering everyone
except the ones we know for sure.
The Seeker's playing us right now.
How does this keep happening
every single time?
[♪ music surges]
[Horseking] The Seeker is always
way ahead of us.
I feel like we're being controlled
by the Seeker.
It really hurt my pride.
At that point,
I didn't care about winning.
I just wanted to catch the Seeker.
I was so annoyed.
[groans]
The Seeker is really smart.
It's so annoying.
If I catch them, I want to punch them.
That's how I felt.
[Pani Bottle] Right now,
the totally innocent ones
are Ddolddol, Jaegyun, and Sanghyun.
It's not me either. I'm totally innocent.
No, it still could be you two.
-[Jimin] It's possible.
-Even if it's only 1%,
it's still a possibility.
[Pani Bottle] It's not impossible,
but we're honestly at 1%.
If I turn out to be the Seeker,
I'll literally cut off my arms and legs.
Maybe it's Dail.
-Come on, why are you doing this?
-[Eunsil] It's you, isn't it?
-Dail, it's you, isn't it?
-[Dail] I wish it were me.
You're making yourself more suspicious.
Just be quiet.
Fine, you can suspect me.
But the more you do,
the more dumb you look.
[♪ music intensifies]
[groans softly]
They're hopeless. For crying out loud.
Gosh, they're so hopeless. [chuckles]
-[Pani Bottle] I'm the same.
-I'll bet my life on it.
If you say that, we'll all do the same.
We'll bet our lives too.
I'll really bet my life on it. Will you?
I will.
[host] According to the rules
of Deadly Tag,
you have become the Seeker.
Now, manipulate the game,
SURVIVE WITHOUT REVEALING YOUR IDENTITY
and create chaos
to prevent the players from winning.
SEEKER PARK JIMIN
Seriously, am I meant to be a spy?
BEFORE THE FIRST MAIN MATCH
[dealer] Please choose a locker number
from 1 to 12 to store your funds.
PLAYERS CHOSE KEYS
AFTER DEPOSITING FUNDS
I'll go with No. 4.
THE IDENTITY OF KEY NO. 4
YOU HAVE BECOME THE SEEKER
[Jimin] It said,
"You're the Seeker," so I thought,
"Am I the only one who got this message?"
"I'm the only one?"
I was really flustered.
But these kinds of games with politics
are pretty much my forte.
And with a battle of wits.
When I saw the mission,
I knew I had to help the Cops win.
MAIN MATCH, "COPS AND ROBBERS"
SEEKER MISSION
I thought it over really quickly.
MAKE THREE COPS WIN
My first thought was,
"Who got the ropes off first?"
1ST: YOUN SANGHYUN
2ND: JANG EUNSIL
Also, Yuk Junseo is a former UDT member,
and this game requires physical strength.
THREE COPS SELECTED
First off, I wanted to make sure
the cops won.
ROUND 1
As soon as Round 1 started,
I got caught so quickly.
SEEKER'S HELP 1
MAKE YOURSELF EASY FOR THE COPS TO FIND
Geez, you scared me.
-[Eunsil clears throat]
-[Jimin] She's good.
I picked good cops.
You're a Drug Criminal.
No, I'm not.
[Eunsil] You're not, even with this?
SEEKER'S HELP 2
WEAK LIES IN INTERROGATION
[Jimin] No, I'm an Assault Criminal.
With lies this obvious,
she must've caught on.
-[Pani Bottle] That's impressive.
-[Dail] You're good.
[ZZONE] The Cops did such a great job.
[Jimin] I was proud of them.
How did the cops get such a good lineup?
It's because I picked them.
Everyone thinks the cops made it happen
on their own, but I set everything up.
I built this whole thing
and made them what they are.
[Sanghyun] Where's Horseking?
PLAYERS RETURN AFTER THE MAIN MATCH
SEEKER PARK JIMIN IS BUSY
BEHIND THE SCENES
THE MAP PROVIDED TO THE SEEKER
[Jimin] The map showed lockers,
a table, and a secret room.
LOCKERS
Then, I noticed a red light
behind the lockers.
So I shoved the lockers
really hard to the side.
[♪ thrilling synth music playing]
THE SECRET SEEKER ROOM
BEHIND THE VOTING ROOM
I had no idea there was a room behind it.
Wow, it was really thrilling.
It felt like I had
an incredible privilege.
[host] Tonight, the first Seeker Vote
will take place.
Select a player
who will face the Elimination Vote.
[Jimin] I thought about
how Kim Ddolddol won the game
by cleverly betraying Joonsu.
-That's why it's easy to frame him.
-Sorry.
It's because we have evidence.
So, I picked Kim Ddolddol.
TARGET: KIM DDOLDDOL
TALKING BEFORE THE SEEKER VOTE
[Jieun] The Seeker
was manipulating the game.
-Just to give my honest opinion,
-[♪ rock music playing]
I have a feeling it's Sanghyun.
[Jimin] He started suspecting Sanghyun,
so I thought, "Thank you."
If he'll put himself out there,
I'm all for it.
-Kim Ddolddol was getting too involved.
-[ZZONE] To be honest,
-I was suspicious of him too.
-I know.
But I think
"CASTING SUSPICION ON DDOLDDOL"
after hearing what Ddolddol said...
[Eunsil] I'm suspicious of Ddolddol too.
I suspected Ddolddol from the start.
[Jimin] Wow, this is great luck.
It'll be perfect for me to pile on.
If we all agree on one person to vote for,
that person will definitely be out.
Yeah, they'll definitely be out.
Then, how about we all vote
for the same person?
I agree with voting for Ddolddol.
[Jimin] I casually suggested it,
and everyone agreed.
I think that took barely a minute.
[dealer] As you successfully cleared
the Seeker mission yesterday,
you receive one extra voting ticket.
That's right. The Seeker gets two.
KIM DDOLDDOL CONFIRMED
AS ELIMINATION CANDIDATE
[Jimin] I expected it.
I picked the person
people would most likely suspect.
Looking back,
I actually picked really well.
[dealer] Please name two players
who will incorrectly tag you.
Shin Jieun and Hwang Jaegyun.
[host] In the previous Main Match,
the Seeker failed.
-[Joonsu] Nice!
-[players cheering]
[♪ ominous music playing]
Great.
[Jimin] My strategy
was basically a fake-out.
[Horseking] For today's Seeker Vote,
I'll say this confidently.
It has to be out of ZZONE,
Jieun, and Jimin.
[Jimin] Horseking seemed to have locked in
who the Seeker could be
and was starting to suspect us.
That makes no sense. No, sorry, sorry.
Not including prison members, right?
It could be someone who is in prison.
Then, the Seeker mission
would be counted as a failure.
[Jimin] Then, the Seeker mission needs
to fail for more suspects to emerge.
Once the prison team gets ruled out,
I thought I'd be at a disadvantage.
That's why I failed
the Seeker mission on purpose.
Because it worked in my favor.
[♪ music intensifies]
And those up for elimination
turned out exactly the way I wanted.
I felt bad, but I had to pull
Sanghyun's card quickly.
So, I chose Sanghyun.
YOUN SANGHYUN CONFIRMED
AS ELIMINATION CANDIDATE AS PLANNED
[players] What?
-[Joonsu] Again? That's crazy.
-[Dail] The Seeker is so smart.
PRETENDING TO BE SURPRISED
[Jimin] I guess
my strategy really paid off.
Could anyone be a better Seeker than me?
I feel like I can keep pushing ahead.
Because I can create
another sacrifice when I need to.
If I keep going like this,
I should be fine going forward.
[Pani Bottle sighs loudly]
-[♪ contemplative music playing]
-The Seeker is pretty good.
The fact that we're getting annoyed
proves that the Seeker's doing a good job.
I know. I'm annoyed too.
[groans]
[sighs in exasperation]
This is getting on my nerves.
[mic feedback]
[host] Tomorrow's Main Match
will be a five-on-five team battle.
[players gasp]
The winning team will receive
20 million won in personal funds
and an Elimination Immunity Pass
for each member.
-[ZZONE] All five survive?
-Five players?
[Pani Bottle] The whole teams advances.
[host] And the losing team
-will all be up for elimination
-[ZZONE gasps loudly]
-and go straight to the Death Match.
-Six people right away.
We're having the Death Match
immediately tomorrow.
[host] The game will take place
around each team's base.
Each team will have one leader
representing them.
-Who will be the leader?
-[Horseking] Who's the leader?
[host] We will announce the team leaders
for tomorrow's Main Match.
Kim Ddolddol.
-I can't handle this pressure! Please!
-[all laughing]
It was too much pressure for me.
Why did I get picked?
Isn't it going to be Pani Bottle?
WHO'S THE OTHER LEADER?
And ZZONE.
-Me?
-[players exclaiming]
What's the criteria for this?
[host] The team leaders
were personally chosen by the Seeker.
[♪ intriguing music playing]
I knew it.
Wow.
[host] The two team leaders will draw lots
to decide the order,
and then take turns selecting
one team member at a time.
[Jaegyun] Oh...
[host] Team selections
will start in an hour.
[beeping]
Man, this is strange.
Why make those two the leaders?
That I don't know.
[Pani Bottle]
The choice of leaders really puzzled me.
Because normally, they'd split up
the two strongest players.
ZZONE wasn't considered a strong player,
so the fact that she became a leader
only made sense if she was the Seeker.
The Seeker would want
to create a strong team.
We know he's not the Seeker.
The Seeker could pick themselves.
ZZONE SUSPECTED AS THE SEEKER
[ZZONE] At first, I was really surprised
when I suddenly became a leader.
I felt like the Seeker suspects
were starting to narrow down.
And it seemed like there was an intention
to include me as a suspect.
[Ddolddol] Kim Ddolddol, ZZONE.
What? Usually, they'd pick people
with similar traits.
Those two are kind of total opposites.
I didn't think Kim Ddolddol and ZZONE
made sense as a leader pairing.
[exasperated sigh]
This is giving me a headache.
This was all part of my bigger plan.
ONE HOUR AGO
[Joonsu] I'm curious
about the game tomorrow.
Where is everybody?
Should I bring Eunsil over?
-[♪ suspicious music playing]
-[Joonsu singing ballad music]
Eunsil...
PARK JIMIN LEAVES THE DINING ROOM
Where's Eunsil?
LOOKING AROUND
This game is really hard.
THE TWO HAVEN'T NOTICED ANYTHING
SHE SNEAKS OUT
PRETENDING TO LOOK FOR EUNSIL
DEADLY TAG
SEEKER RULES
JIMIN SECRETLY ENTERED THE SEEKER ROOM
[exhales] This is driving me crazy.
THIRD MAIN MATCH
SEEKER MISSION
SELECT TWO TEAM LEADERS
WHO WILL FORM THE TEAMS
[whispers] Leader...
PICKED KIM DDOLDDOL IMMEDIATELY
AS THE FIRST LEADER
First of all, the prison group,
Kim Ddolddol, Yang Dail, and Pani Bottle,
seemed to have a really strong bond.
They'd been sticking together all day,
so I figured those three
were definitely going to team up.
But I didn't want to join their team.
Honestly, I wanted to be the one
picking the team members.
But people were already getting
a little suspicious of me.
So I thought about who would choose me...
PICKED ZZONE AS THE SECOND LEADER
I felt like I could trust ZZONE the most
since we had been sharing a room
from the very beginning.
And us girls talk about
a lot of things in our room.
[ZZONE] The prison alliance
seems really strong.
[Jimin] Their bond is no joke.
I think we need to have each other's backs
if we're going to get through the game.
I agree.
[Eunsil] We need
to eliminate them all quickly,
starting with the prison family.
Since ZZONE was on the list
of possible Seekers,
I thought picking her could be a way
to make people suspect she was the Seeker.
That's why I picked ZZONE.
THINGS SEEM TO GO
ACCORDING TO JIMIN'S PLAN
Is there really anything to discuss?
Isn't it up to whoever's picking?
[Jaegyun] What's there to talk about?
GETS UP
We're supposed to talk about
who will be on which team.
SLOWLY WALKING
-After drawing lots...
-[♪ suspicious music playing]
SIGNALS KIM DDOLDDOL WITH A HAND GESTURE
[indistinct chatter]
[Pani Bottle] It might be hard
to get the prison group together.
-I wonder if we can.
-[Pani Bottle] Right? That'd be ideal.
YANG DAIL WALKS OUT SHORTLY AFTER
[Jimin] They kept passing by
to have their own discussions.
I picked really well.
[Pani Bottle] Let's go upstairs.
GLANCES
[Jimin] Look.
JIMIN BEGINS HER OPERATION
-They'll team up for sure, right?
-Sorry?
Those three will definitely
team up, right?
Is that possible?
Not really, if I pick one of them.
If ZZONE picks one of them,
those three can't stick together.
[ZZONE] It'll divide them up.
They'll assume that I won't pick them.
The entire five-member team
-will go to the Death Match.
-[ZZONE] Right.
So maybe the best move
is to take them all out.
Let them stick together
and take them all out?
-Let those three team up like that?
-[Jimin] Yes.
This is when we need Sanghyun.
[♪ amusing music playing]
We sent him away.
Poor Sanghyun.
[Horseking] Sanghyun
was a really strong player.
[Eunsil] I miss him.
[Pani Bottle sighs]
[Pani Bottle] They really
complicated things.
[Ddolddol] The three of us
trust each other more than anyone else.
It's best if us three
are on the same team.
[Pani Bottle] We have to stick together.
Who else do you think would work well?
Aside from the three of us,
Yuk Junseo, Horseking, or Jaegyun.
Horseking or Jaegyun?
Since it's a team match, I want to team up
with Pani Bottle and Yang Dail,
my prison mates who I've built
a strong bond with.
And we should bring one strong guy.
Maybe someone athletic,
like Horseking, Yuk Junseo, or Jaegyun?
The guys will be split up
since ZZONE is going to pick
-the strong ones.
-[Pani Bottle] Right.
Then, who should I pick first?
-In my opinion...
-Jaegyun?
If you win the draw...
-Us first?
-No, not us.
Pick Yuk Junseo first.
-As for Yuk Junseo,
-[♪ contemplative music playing]
these games require
some physical strength, but...
I still believe we need a strong player.
For the next pick,
who first between you two?
Then, you should pick Jaegyun.
-What about you two?
-[Dail] You can pick us later.
But I think the three of us
have to team up, no matter what.
If the three of us join forces,
I think we're the strongest team
even without players like Yuk Junseo.
And Sanghyun's not around.
If they take one of us,
we're in big trouble.
[Pani Bottle] I really wanted us three
on the same team.
ZZONE definitely knows
that the three of us are tightly united.
So I figured she'd try
to split us up somehow.
I'm worried it won't be easy
for us to stick together.
[Pani Bottle] I think you should
try to pick us first, if possible.
That's what I think.
That way, we can work as a team.
But what if she picks Yuk Junseo,
Jaegyun, and Horseking all in a row?
What then?
THE PRISON ALLIANCE RETURNS
TO THE MAIN HALL
What are you going to do, Ddolddol?
-Are the three of you sticking together?
-[Ddolddol] Sorry?
Let me tell you something in advance.
-If you pick me for your team...
-Yes?
Then, I'm going to troll.
-I'll go to the Death Match.
-[♪ tense music playing]
-I like trolls.
-[Pani Bottle] I'm just telling you.
I'm just saying, "Please don't pick me."
If I'm not on Ddolddol's team,
I'll just give up tomorrow
and throw the game.
[Horseking] I thought
he was being way too pushy.
What's wrong with him?
Why would he say that now?
He really got on my nerves.
Even without us, I don't think
it would create an imbalance.
I agree with you, but it's fun.
-It's not fun for me.
-[laughs]
[ZZONE] It was seriously annoying.
So I wanted to break up the alliance
between the three prison players.
[dealer] We will begin team selection.
-Ms. ZZONE, you have the first pick.
-[♪ rock music playing]
Please name one team member
you would like to select.
The order is really important.
If he picks first, then I pick,
then he picks again, and I pick again,
my options can change a lot
depending on my position in the order.
-I'll pick this one.
-[ZZONE] You first. It's 50-50.
-You want this one?
-[ZZONE] Yes.
-[Ddolddol] Want to switch?
-Shall we?
[Ddolddol] One, two, three.
You go first, ZZONE.
ZZONE GETS THE RIGHT FOR FIRST PICK
[ZZONE] When I drew the 1 card,
I thought, "I did it!
I have a chance to win this time."
I was so happy.
I'll...
-What's going to happen?
-[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Will she sabotage or use her own strategy?
[Jimin] I picked ZZONE.
I really hope she does well.
I'll pick Horseking.
ZZONE PICKS HORSEKING FIRST
For a physical battle, I definitely needed
Horseking on the same team.
Ironically enough,
I wanted to be on ZZONE's team.
There's a certain synergy between people,
and Ddolddol is somewhat...
He's been too talkative since day one.
I noticed that he's very vocal
and has his own strong opinions.
That reckless confidence
and strategy without solid reasoning
could actually become a liability,
so I was happy ZZONE chose me.
[Jimin] Horseking.
[Ddolddol] ZZONE picked Horseking first.
So I gave it a lot of thought.
I'll pick Yuk Junseo.
Who could go up against Horseking?
So I chose Yuk Junseo.
[dealer] Yuk Junseo has been selected.
KIM DDOLDDOL PICKS YUK JUNSEO FIRST
They're similar types.
Physically strong players. [laughs]
[ZZONE] Who should I pick?
Go with your instincts.
You have to go with your gut.
I'll pick...
Yang Dail.
[Ddolddol] What's happening?
I really panicked at that moment.
I thought, "Hold on,
what do I do now? I'm screwed."
[Pani Bottle sighs] This is
driving me insane.
When I heard that, I was irritated.
[Jimin] I clearly told her the prison
members were our enemies.
How could she pick Yang Dail?
What's she even thinking?
-Okay.
-[dealer] ZZONE has chosen Yang Dail.
ZZONE PICKS YANG DAIL SECOND
Dail seems like someone who stays calm
and won't lose his composure easily.
I thought he'd make rational decisions
in critical moments.
Also, I knew we needed
to break them apart eventually.
I was really happy watching them
get split apart one by one.
[Dail] I'm not sure if she picked me
to separate me
from Ddolddol and Pani Bottle.
To me, the prison alliance
was meant to last until we left prison.
LAST NIGHT, JAEGYUN AND ZZONE WERE TALKING
DAIL NATURALLY JOINS THEM
[Dail] What's that?
[ZZONE] We can see
after returning from prison.
[Dail] I was so stressed out in there.
Personally,
I know Pani Bottle
and Ddolddol aren't bad people.
But if I'm around people like that,
I don't think I could stand it.
Because they're unpredictable?
[Dail] If I'm with people
who might do something unpredictable,
I'd have to keep an eye on them
all the time if we're on the same team.
And that would stress me out.
I got involved with Pani Bottle
in the first round
and ended up being called "Mad Dail."
THE TWO CLASHED ON DAY ONE
DURING TEAM SELECTION MEETING
If you win the draw...
-Us first?
-No, not us.
Pick Yuk Junseo first.
Then, you should pick Jaegyun.
DAIL MADE THEM NOT PICK HIM
The alliance was only meant to last
until we got out of prison
and made it back into daylight.
Now, I can form a new team
and try to work well with them.
No matter what team I'm on,
I'll play my hardest.
Then, I'll go with Pani Bottle.
Then, I can't give up.
KIM DDOLDDOL PICKS PANI BOTTLE SECOND
-It's not going to be easy.
-It'll be tough.
Dail ended up there.
Pick Jaegyun, no matter what.
I'll pick Hwang Jaegyun.
[Ddolddol] What's her deal? It annoyed me.
-[dealer] ZZONE has chosen Hwang Jaegyun.
-[♪ tense synth music playing]
ZZONE PICKS HWANG JAEGYUN THIRD
I'll go with Jang Eunsil.
[dealer] Kim Ddolddol
has chosen Jang Eunsil.
KIM DDOLDDOL PICKS JANG EUNSIL THIRD
We don't have any choices left.
Whoever's left will join us.
THE REMAINING PLAYERS
PARK JIMIN, LEE JOONSU
Which one should we pick?
[Horseking] We don't know
what game it'll be.
[Jaegyun] Exactly. We don't know.
We should bring Joonsu.
If it's a physical game,
that'd be a good choice.
-Joonsu is unexpectedly clever, right?
-ZZONE, please pick your last member.
No, he's not very helpful.
Right, you have a point.
He's not mentally tough.
[Dail] I think that's really crucial.
[Horseking sighs]
[ZZONE] We were debating
because we wanted Joonsu for his strength,
but he might not be the right choice
when it comes to brains and politics.
Jimin, on the other hand,
isn't physically strong,
but she's strong with strategy.
[Horseking] We might need someone
with more experience.
[Dail] Then...
They're taking their time.
It's not a good feeling.
It doesn't feel good.
I've never been treated that way before
in my entire life.
I felt really hurt.
[Joonsu] At first, I knew they could
take some time to talk it through,
but after five minutes went by,
I started getting annoyed.
Is it really that hard to decide?
Ugh...
It's so hard.
I think we should go with this option.
[Horseking] You think so?
[ZZONE] I'll pick...
[♪ music intensifies]
Lee Joonsu.
[dealer] ZZONE has chosen Lee Joonsu.
ZZONE'S LAST PICK IS LEE JOONSU
[Jimin sighs]
ZZONE didn't pick me in the end.
After what happened with her,
I definitely felt betrayed by ZZONE.
I wanted us to come together once
and prove that we could win.
I thought that would shift the whole game
and turn us into a team
that people would be wary of.
But ZZONE probably saw things differently.
She seemed to make the choice
that gave her
the best chance of surviving.
And as a result,
many of the physically strong players
ended up joining her side.
I never wanted to be on that team,
but I somehow ended up joining
Ddolddol's team.
[dealer] Then automatically,
-Park Jimin will join Kim Ddolddol's team.
-Okay.
[Ddolddol in English] Welcome.
[Jimin in Korean] I was frustrated.
[sighs in exasperation]
I started thinking that choosing ZZONE
as the leader was a mistake.
[ZZONE] I was torn until the last minute.
My gut told me that teaming up with Jimin
would have helped more strategically.
[Horseking] What do you think?
TEAM MEETING BEFORE FINAL SELECTION
Pani Bottle and Jimin
aren't on good terms. [chuckles softly]
[ZZONE] Ah, that's true.
[Jaegyun] Putting them on the same team
could be a good move.
[ZZONE] Jimin and Pani Bottle
don't like each other.
[Jimin] Pani Bottle...
I don't think we click at all.
-[ZZONE] That's so funny.
-[Jimin] It'll be fucking hard to play
together with Pani Bottle.
[ZZONE] Really?
[Pani Bottle] We need to get rid
of Park Jimin eventually.
I just don't like her.
She talked down and got mad at me
at the first Main Hall.
Since then, I've never liked her.
I can't fucking stand her.
This is a first.
JIMIN AND PANI BOTTLE DON'T GET ALONG
[ZZONE] These selected teams are crazy.
If we put Jimin and Pani Bottle together,
our chances of winning
would be much higher.
After a lot of thought, I chose Joonsu.
TEAM ZZONE
HORSEKING, DAIL, JAEGYUN, JOONSU
TEAM DDOLDDOL
JUNSEO, PANI BOTTLE, EUNSIL, JIMIN
[mic feedback]
[host] We will now reveal
the third Main Match of Deadly Tag.
The third Main Match is...
"Kingmaker."
"Kingmaker?"
[host] "Kingmaker" is a game
where teams predict each other's ranks
and go through card battles
to eliminate the opposing team's cards.
Each team chooses
one of two bases on the game area.
Before the game begins,
each team will hold a discussion
and distribute a total of 11 rank cards
among its members.
The deck consists of one King,
the highest-ranking card,
nine numbered cards,
and one Joker, the lowest-ranking card.
The higher the number,
the stronger the card.
The King card beats every other card.
However, the King card loses to the Joker,
the lowest-ranking card.
-So only the Joker can beat the King.
-Right.
-And the 1 beats the Joker?
-That's right.
The Joker can't beat any card
except the King.
[host] Each player receives
two rank cards,
while the player holding the Joker
receives three cards.
However, the King and the Joker
cannot be held by the same player.
Players are not allowed to transfer
or exchange cards during the game.
"Kingmaker" consists of two phases,
the Battle Round and the Strategy Round.
Once the Battle Round begins,
players can tag members
of the opposing team.
When a tag occurs, the two players
will move to the nearest Dealer Room
to conduct a card battle.
In a card battle,
each player secretly hands
one card to the dealer.
The winning card is removed from play,
and the winner takes
the losing player's card.
If you win with the King card,
you get to keep the King card.
If both players reveal cards
of the same rank, nothing happens.
Any player who runs out of rank cards
is immediately removed from the game.
Gosh, that's brutal.
[host] After each Battle Round,
there is a five-minute Strategy Round.
Once those five minutes end,
another Battle Round begins.
This cycle continues until one team
captures the opposing team's King card.
The first team to do so wins.
This has nothing to do
with physical strength.
It's all about using your brain.
[sighs]
[host] In addition,
each team has 15 symbols.
What? Symbols?
Teams must protect their own symbols
while stealing the opposition's symbols.
The number of symbols captured
determines the advantages the team earns.
Oh...
Symbols... We need to capture them.
While playing the card game?
The symbols are important and all,
but there's no need to focus on them.
-Let's win the card battles...
-[Jimin] Right.
...and take out all the opposing players.
[Jimin] The Joker is the key.
-Once you take the King, it's over.
-Exactly.
You chase each other's tails
and end up back where you started.
This is basically a complicated game
of rock, paper, scissors.
Since it's a card game,
I thought using our brains
would be important.
We need to decide right now
who will take King and Joker cards.
Do we give it to someone fast
or someone who looks like an easy target
-and make it a battle of wits?
-[ZZONE] A battle of wits.
Before anything else,
what do you think they'll give Junseo?
-I think he'll get the King.
-[Dail] You think so?
Why do I feel like
they won't give Junseo the King?
We'll need to use our heads
more than we think in this game.
When Junseo becomes absorbed,
he stops thinking logically.
You need to keep your cool
in this card game.
They'd never give the King to someone
who loses their composure.
I think they'll give him
an 8 or 9 instead.
Instead of taking some weak card
and risking having it stolen,
I'd rather give Junseo an 8 or 9.
Then, Junseo needs
to keep dodging everyone like hell
as if he has the King.
You know that thing you do when your eyes
turn red and you run like mad?
That should be enough.
Take an 8 or 9, act fucking cocky
as if you're the King.
-"Cocky."
-That's fucking funny.
Then, take the Joker later on
and beat the King.
-You'll be the hero.
-That's so cool.
[Ddolddol] That's going to be so cool.
-Let's make him the real King.
-[Jimin] That's so cool.
Once we identify who their King is,
we'll have to chase them down to tag them.
So they're going to give
the Joker and the King
to someone who's athletic or fast.
Jaegyun or Horseking.
-I think it'll be one of the two.
-Yes.
But that's a little too one-dimensional.
Fast people get the King or the Joker.
-Isn't that obvious?
-There's a reason.
To catch the King with the Joker,
you have to run fast.
-Fast runners can catch up.
-But think about this.
If we work together
to keep chasing Horseking,
when he's exhausted, you can tag him.
-So I think...
-Right.
If we coordinate, we can still catch them.
[Pani Bottle] Being fast
gives us more options.
We can choose
when we want to fight or not.
PANI BOTTLE DISAGREES WITH JIMIN
If that's not an option,
we need to think about
whether we need to give a key role
to someone who doesn't run well.
[Jimin] Don't you think
they might try to tag me
since it'll seem like I have weaker cards?
Or wouldn't it be better
if I beat everyone as the King?
JIMIN REFUSES TO BACK DOWN
When I heard that, I thought,
"What's her deal?"
I had no idea what to make of her.
Something about her is so weird.
I had the Seeker mission.
[sighs in exasperation]
This is driving me crazy.
The mission was to compete against
the opposing team at least three times.
The Joker was a card that would let me
play three times, no matter what.
There was a high chance
of beating the King.
The King and the Joker
were perfect for me.
You need to win the battle of wits too.
If you have the King and 6,
you need to read the opponent
-to play the 6 correctly.
-[Ddolddol] Right.
JIMIN APPEALS FOR KING OR JOKER
Are you good?
I tried to convince our leader
that I can bluff convincingly.
Since the timing
of when you play a card is crucial,
I thought the King and the Joker
should go to people
who are strong in a battle of wits.
It wouldn't be a bad idea if Jimin did it.
Or are those roles too important?
It's kind of risky.
Let's narrow it down to two for now
and decide tomorrow.
If we don't settle it,
we'll repeat this tomorrow.
[Jimin] We'll talk about it tomorrow.
Sleep tight.
[Ddolddol] I'm so tired.
[Pani Bottle sighs] I'm against
giving the King to Park Jimin.
Me too. I can't really trust her.
If we fail, we'll end up
in the Death Match. It's too risky.
-What should we give to Jimin?
-[♪ contemplative music playing]
It's too risky
to give a crucial card to her.
We should rule out giving the King
or the Joker to anyone who isn't fast.
I'm completely against it.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[crows cawing]
[Ddolddol] Oh my, what are these reeds?
[ZZONE] Wait, this is an actual school.
[♪ rock music playing]
[Jaegyun] Any player I considered
a threat? There was no one among them.
[Dail] I honestly think I'm not someone
people can easily take down.
[Horseking] I'll show you
what a real team is like
and how big of a role I'll play.
[Ddolddol] Just at a glance,
they're a cute girl with pink hair
and four big dudes.
They don't look like much.
Our team will beat them.
[Junseo] I'm someone who hates losing,
and I absolutely refuse to lose.
[Eunsil] Our entire team
is fired up right now.
I believe we can crush them.
[mic feedback]
[host] We will explain the Kingmaker area
and the symbols.
The "Kingmaker" area consists
of the Red Team Base, Blue Team Base,
and the Neutral Zone.
Each team has 15 symbols in total.
Eight are hidden in each base,
and seven are hidden in the Neutral Zone.
Shouldn't we start with the Neutral Zone
and win that area?
It might be worth quickly searching
-the Neutral Zone.
-There are seven there.
[host] Each base has a map
showing 14 locations
marked by their team symbol,
while one location remains undisclosed.
Players must find and secure
the opposing team's symbols,
bring them back to the Dealer Room
in their own base,
and destroy the symbols.
Once a team captures four symbols,
the player holding the opposing team's
4 card will be revealed.
If the 4 card has already been taken out,
the next higher card will be revealed.
Once a team captures seven symbols,
they will obtain a Shuffle Ticket.
A Shuffle Ticket allows a player
to exchange one card
that is not the King with a teammate.
Once a team retrieves 10 symbols,
the opposing team's highest-ranking card
that is not the King card
can be eliminated.
Once we find four symbols,
we can start crushing them.
[Pani Bottle] If both sides go,
"Let's tag everyone and end this,"
then the symbols won't matter.
That's not how it'll go at first.
We'll all size each other up,
so symbols matter.
It's a huge variable.
[host] You will now explore the bases.
BLUE TEAM BASE
[Ddolddol] It's so big.
[Junseo] It's bigger than expected.
DEALER ROOM ON FAR RIGHT SIDE
OF MAIN ENTRANCE
[Ddolddol] I guess
we smash them with a hammer.
[ZZONE] It'll be hard to find symbols.
SPACIOUS BLUE TEAM BASE
[Dail] This will be good for hiding.
[ZZONE] It seems like
a good defensive spot.
No, if you hide,
it allows the other team to attack more.
[Ddolddol] In the professor's office,
-there's an opening.
-[Junseo] There's a hole.
KIM DDOLDDOL
[ZZONE] Doesn't it feel too empty?
It's basically impossible to sneak into.
[Dail] It's so wide open
that if someone tries to sneak in,
we could miss them
if we drop our guard even for a second.
It feels like we'd get completely exposed.
RED TEAM BASE
To stay defensive and dodge them,
this place is way better.
RED TEAM BASE IS FILLED WITH OBSTACLES
[Dail] We have to open each one?
There has to be a symbol here.
[ZZONE] Right, Horseking will need
to show us some parkour.
-[Ddolddol] What is this place?
-[Junseo] Board games?
[Ddolddol] Something about this
feels suspicious.
-It feels like a Death Match area.
-[Junseo] Right.
The inside felt complicated.
There were much more obstacles
on the way in than the Blue Team Base,
so it might be better
for hiding and defense.
This leads to the Neutral Zone.
[Ddolddol] When we go this way,
-it goes like this.
-[Junseo] Right.
It's much more closer to the Neutral Zone.
PARKING LOT
REED FIELD
NEUTRAL ZONE
13,112 SQUARE METERS (4,000 PYEONG)
Well, at first glance,
the Red Team Base feels
a lot narrower overall.
This one's bigger.
The pros and cons are clear.
-[Dail] Right.
-That place is very closed off.
-[Dail] It's enclosed.
-[ZZONE] It's narrow...
"RED TEAM BASE"
-...and packed with objects.
-[Dail] Yes.
You have to dig around a lot.
This is much bigger.
BLUE TEAM BASE
-[Dail] A lot of hiding spots.
-[Joonsu] There are four entrances.
[Horseking] The Red Team Base
is easier for defense?
-[Dail] It's narrower.
-[Horseking] Ah.
If you try to take symbols from there,
it'll be a lot easier to get tagged.
-[ZZONE] Right.
-Because the entrance is narrow.
Since the Red Team Base
is much smaller than Blue's,
it's way easier to defend.
[mic feedback]
[host] It's time to choose the team bases.
Team Kim Ddolddol has the higher total
of personal funds,
so they get first choice.
All right.
We'll choose the Red Team Base
as our home base.
[Dail] Hmm, I was really disappointed.
We didn't have the option of choosing
our base, so it is what it is.
[host] Both teams, head to your bases
and begin your strategy meeting.
[Junseo] Feels like they'll go with
the standard game plan.
-[Ddolddol] Right?
-[Junseo] Yes.
I have a feeling
one of their fastest players
is holding the King.
I agree with that.
[Ddolddol] I think the King should be
among Yang Dail, Horseking, and Jaegyun.
I bet Junseo and Eunsil
-each have a high-ranking card.
-Yeah.
As for Eunsil, it's best
to have the King tag her.
-I bet Eunsil...
-[Jaegyun] Never.
-...doesn't have one.
-[Dail] They'd never give her the King.
Who do you think has the Joker?
Joker and King are probably
with players who are either fast
or completely off the radar.
That's most likely.
The King has to be played
-aggressively.
-Yes.
The odds are Junseo has it.
The most likely person is Junseo too.
It has to be Yuk Junseo.
Yuk Junseo had to be the one
holding the King.
Or someone brilliant.
But I don't think they have anyone
who's really brilliant.
You should play aggressively, Junseo.
-Okay.
-Pretend to be the King.
Junseo should go all out and wild.
-[Ddolddol] It's a bluff.
-I'll take this first.
BLUE TEAM'S GUESS
YUK JUNSEO
I'll just be the King.
They'll probably go,
"The leader can't be the King."
They'll probably assume
-I was given the Joker.
-[Pani Bottle] Right.
KIM DDOLDDOL
The King has to be fast,
but they also need to win mind games.
So I thought he'd be suited for the King.
[Ddolddol] They're definitely expecting
Eunsil to charge in aggressively.
So we could give the Joker to Eunsil
and then move it to Jimin.
Or we could give Jimin the Joker
and if the King happens to...
They already have a certain image of me,
so they'll assume
I'm just a throwaway card.
I wanted to get the Joker.
Think outside the box.
The card should go to someone
nobody would expect,
so the other team can't predict it.
WHO HAS THE JOKER ON THE RED TEAM?
[Jaegyun] So Horseking
is definitely taking that [bleep], right?
[all] Yes.
[Dail] I'll take the 8 card.
[Jaegyun] Then, I'll take [bleep].
I'm sure I'll get caught,
so I should take a lower number.
[Jaegyun] So your role
is to keep bluffing.
Keep these two hidden
-as much as possible.
-[ZZONE] Okay.
[Jaegyun] So we're set on these numbers?
[Horseking] Yes. We can't change it now.
-This should be our cheat code.
-[ZZONE] I bet they won't expect this.
KIM DDOLDDOL, YUK JUNSEO, PANI BOTTLE,
JANG EUNSIL, PARK JIMIN
ZZONE, HORSEKING, YANG DAIL,
HWANG JAEGYUN, LEE JOONSU
[rustling]
[host] The "Kingmaker" Battle Round
starts now.
-[Horseking in English] Let's go.
-[Jaegyun in Korean] Let's go.
[ZZONE] Way to go!
[Horseking] You have to put on an act.
-[ZZONE laughs]
-[Joonsu] This will be fun as hell.
Follow me, follow me.
-[Junseo] Did you bring the notebook?
-[Ddolddol] Yes.
-[Eunsil] Search first?
-[Ddolddol] Yeah, search first.
There they are.
-They're running over.
-[Horseking] They're coming together.
-[ZZONE] They're running over.
-[Horseking] They're coming as a group.
-[Ddolddol] Go to the right.
-[Pani Bottle] To the right?
[Ddolddol] Go right and to the side door.
RED TEAM RUSHES IN RIGHT AWAY
-[Horseking] Dail! Dail!
-[ZZONE] They're coming.
-[Joonsu] Horseking!
-[Jaegyun] Dail!
They're all coming together!
I thought, "What are they doing?"
The five of them were all coming in
like some morning running crew.
Even when we were facing each other,
they ignored me like I was invisible.
Hang on!
[ZZONE laughs] What kind
of strategy is this?
GOING STRAIGHT AND IGNORING BLUE TEAM
I was so startled. I thought they were
coming in to tag someone.
THEY ENTER BLUE TEAM BASE IN AN INSTANT
[panting]
[Junseo] The Red Team's plan at the start
was to move together
and play aggressively.
We planned to look for the symbols boldly,
as if everyone was the King.
FOUND A SYMBOL
[♪ rock music playing]
[Ddolddol] Okay.
Let's go.
SYMBOLS CAN ONLY BE BROKEN
AT YOUR OWN BASE
[Jimin] I'll take from here.
[Pani Bottle] Pass it to me.
MOVING SYMBOL TO THE RED TEAM BASE
[Horseking] Over there! He's taking one!
RED TEAM BASE DEALER ROOM
RED TEAM DESTROYS ONE SYMBOL
[alarm blaring]
-[host] Tag confirmed.
-Tag?
Fuck, who is it?
[host] All other players,
please return to your team's base.
What the heck? Who is it?
FIRST TAG
HORSEKING
JANG EUNSIL
[Horseking] Wait! Over there!
He's taking one!
LOST SYMBOL TOO EASILY
TO SURPRISE ATTACK
I didn't know what was going on at first.
In any case,
I wanted to leave them with one card.
So...
RED TEAM KEEPS IGNORING BLUE TEAM
-Tag.
-[alarm blaring]
HORSEKING TAGS EUNSIL
[host] Tag confirmed.
If you tagged me, we should go.
[Horseking] But she was so confident.
I was really thrown off and confused,
I wondered, "What is going on?"
Where does she get the nerve? How?
[dealer] Both players,
please submit your cards.
[Horseking exhales sharply]
HORSEKING AND EUNSIL HAND IN THEIR CARDS
UNFAZED
[Horseking] What is this strategy?
[dealer] We will check the cards.
JANG EUNSIL, HORSEKING
[Eunsil] The 7 was a high card,
so I thought I could beat him.
Horseking? Why would he tag Eunsil?
RED TEAM IS CONVINCED THEY'LL WIN
Why did he tag her?
He's going to regret it.
Let's check our phones.
Her 7 lost to Horseking. Eunsil lost.
EUNSIL
I LOST TO HORSEKING WITH A 7
[dealer] Horseking has won.
JANG EUNSIL'S 7 CARD IS ELIMINATED
SIGH
Maybe Horseking has the King.
I don't think Horseking is the King.
The King would be lying low.
-I think he has a 9.
-[Pani Bottle] Could this be real?
This is really confusing.
It says Horseking has a 9.
-What is this?
-[Ddolddol] Someone dropped it.
[♪ contemplative music playing]
10 MINUTES AGO
[Pani Bottle] I was on my way
back to our base.
I was going down the left path.
I found a notebook on the ground.
I opened it and saw things scribbled down,
but I couldn't make out the words.
It could be something,
so I took it just in case.
It's a completely ridiculous gamble,
but this lost notebook could be legit.
No, that can't be.
-For real?
-[Pani Bottle] It could be fake.
But it says, "Horseking, 1, 9."
It looks like Joonsu's.
It says, "I want to go home."
[Pani Bottle] "Just fucking" what?
-"Seven boxes. Fuck"?
-[Jimin] It's Joonsu's notebook.
NOTEBOOK SEEMS TO BE JOONSU'S
[Ddolddol] I don't think
we can believe this.
Should we keep it as a reference?
[Jimin] Yeah, just as a reference.
[Ddolddol] It was clearly
Joonsu's notebook.
But it had the opposing team's ranks
listed inside.
It looked like
they had written down their ranks
in the notebook during their meeting.
It said Horseking had a 9 and 1
and Jaegyun was the King.
This seems pretty convincing. But hold on.
Let me see.
[Jimin] Jaegyun is the King?
HORSEKING: 9, 1
JAEGYUN: KING, 6
They really made this look convincing.
-They made it like what we would've done
-[Jimin] Yeah.
to make it annoying as well.
It does look convincing.
It's so convincing,
and things are going as written.
[Jimin] I believed the notebook was legit
because I saw Joonsu looking for something
after the first round.
Plus, Horseking didn't hesitate
to tag early on.
[gasps] I thought, "What's this?"
The King wouldn't be acting
that aggressively at the start.
I think this is legit.
Yeah.
They decided to have the 9 get involved.
Then, is this real... Hell, this is hard.
HORSEKING: 9, 1
JAEGYUN: KING, 6
Then, I'll check Horseking.
Isn't it too risky?
Horseking could be either the 9 or King.
Still, if I verify him,
we can either rule out
-or be sure he's the King.
-[Jimin] Right,
That's true.
Junseo should tag Horseking this time.
RED TEAM'S TARGET: HORSEKING
[Horseking] What the heck?
MEANWHILE, BLUE TEAM
[Horseking] Their strategy seems strange.
[Jaegyun] What about it?
Why would they just charge in?
I wondered,
"How many moves ahead did they plan?"
"Isn't this too elaborate?"
I'm wondering what their plan was.
-They all came at once.
-They came together.
We didn't even stop them.
It doesn't make sense
for them to come at us like that.
It makes no sense. I was startled.
I remember thinking,
"What's gotten into them?"
BOTH TEAMS ARE CONFUSED
They all came, so I was confused.
Eunsil got tagged by me, right?
Let's get rid of her.
Once you run into Eunsil,
-just tag her.
-I will.
Yes, that's my plan.
Once one of them gets eliminated...
-[ZZONE] They'll fall like dominoes.
-...it'll put us way ahead.
[Jaegyun] You go after Eunsil.
She doesn't have the King.
BLUE TEAM'S TARGET: EUNSIL
Are we starting now?
Will we hear the alarm?
AFTER 5-MINUTE TEAM MEETING,
SIREN SIGNALS NEW ROUND
-I hate that alarm.
-Let's go.
[alarm blaring]
I'll tag Horseking.
[Horseking] Let's look around for now.
[host] The Battle Round has begun.
[Horseking] Search around.
We'll keep watch here.
-They're walking toward us!
-They're coming!
-Horseking sees us.
-Let's go to the Neutral Zone.
Okay.
There are four on this side!
-[ZZONE] I don't see Eunsil.
-[Horseking] Four here!
Eunsil's not there?
-No, she's hiding.
-I don't see her.
BLUE TEAM'S PLAN HITS A SNAG
RED TEAM BASE, 2ND FLOOR
[Eunsil] I lost one card,
so I couldn't afford to take any risks.
We decided I should hide
and wait for our chance.
So, I hid somewhere out of sight.
[Ddolddol] How about we act like
we're not tagging Horseking
then suddenly go for him?
[Junseo] Pretend we're searching.
This way.
[Ddolddol] This way?
-Should we check the furniture?
-[Junseo] Yes.
THEY PLAN TO BAIT HORSEKING
-[Ddolddol] Shall we go in here?
-[Junseo] Yes.
[Ddolddol] Let's get inside.
[Horseking] They're searching over there.
We'll search here.
-[Jaegyun] We should too.
-[ZZONE] Let's hurry
-and find them.
-[Jaegyun] Let's search.
Dail, let's search.
BLUE TEAM SEARCHES FOR SYMBOLS
AS A BACKUP PLAN
[Horseking] We don't have any yet!
Searching the reeds is no joke.
AND RED TEAM IS WATCHING
[♪ tense music playing]
[Horseking] Junseo's coming.
Junseo's coming.
[Jimin] We need to get Horseking.
RED TEAM CLOSES IN ON HORSEKING
[Ddolddol] Wait a moment.
[Horseking] I'm not going to do it.
[Junseo] Since I had to find out
what card Horseking had,
I was waiting for the right moment.
Wait, I need someone to watch my back.
Jaegyun! Hey, Dail!
I need you to cover me.
You have to get my back, Jaegyun!
BLUE TEAM FOUND A SYMBOL
[♪ rock music playing]
[Jaegyun] I found it.
[♪ music continues playing]
A SYMBOL HIDDEN IN THE REEDS
[Horseking] Let's pull back. Pull back.
[Jimin] Fuck.
[Dail] Junseo is running!
Junseo's behind you!
-[Jimin] Watch out!
-[Ddolddol] Be careful
DISTANCE CREATED INSTANTLY
[Jaegyun] I handed Horseking the symbol
while he was being chased by Junseo.
SYMBOL HANDED TO HORSEKING
BLUE TEAM DESTROYS ONE SYMBOL
It's impossible to catch Horseking.
SYMBOL DESTRUCTION STATUS
FAILED TO TAKE DOWN HORSEKING
MEANWHILE
JOONSU IS LOOKING FOR SOMETHING
[frustrated groan]
[Pani Bottle] Who is it?
Joonsu was coming toward me.
He kept looking around.
And that was the exact spot
where the notebook was found.
Well, look at this.
Should we go our separate ways? [laughs]
Joonsu! Get him.
[Joonsu sighs]
JOONSU TAGS PANI BOTTLE
-[alarm blaring]
-[Joonsu] I got him!
[host] Tag confirmed.
I found it strange that he tagged me.
Why would he tag me?
Since I considered him a weaker player,
-I was even more confused.
-[♪ mysterious music playing]
I don't think they would've given
Joonsu an important card.
[Joonsu] Did you make a choice?
I'm thinking.
[Joonsu] I'll go first then.
This is mine. Joonsu's card.
LEE JOONSU HANDS IN A CARD
[sighs wearily]
[Pani Bottle] I was sure
he wasn't the King,
and the Joker was even less likely.
So I used a 2 to test the waters.
[dealer] We will announce the results.
Lee Joonsu has won.
[Pani Bottle] I'm good to go, right?
PANI BOTTLE'S 2 GOES TO JOONSU
Joonsu won.
[Junseo] It's fine.
Only two cards are out.
[Jimin] And what Joonsu took was a 2.
He played either a 4 or 7.
If he'd played a 7,
then he only has a 4 and 2.
It means he's weak as fuck.
[Dail] Joonsu has a different number now.
-[ZZONE] Right.
-[Jaegyun] Yes, he does.
Joonsu's got a 2 and 4.
Yes, if they go after him
to beat his 2 or 4,
one of us has to come help him.
Then, I'll avoid them.
-Yeah, avoid them.
-Avoid them.
I think the notebook is correct.
Horseking kept telling Jaegyun,
"Jaegyun! I need you to cover me."
"I need you to protect me."
He was saying things like that.
Wait, I need someone to watch my back.
Jaegyun! Hey, Dail!
I need you to cover me.
HORSEKING ASKED JAEGYUN FOR HELP
I think Horseking was afraid
of getting tagged by the King.
[Jimin] Right.
[Ddolddol] Then,
only the King could protect him.
Would he ask the Joker to protect him? No.
If we identify who King is,
that's all we need.
Tagging Horseking and Jaegyun
should reveal the answer.
JAEGYUN: KING, 6
The four of us should go together...
-Let's move together.
-...one after another.
-Let's go as a group.
-[Ddolddol] Attack in waves.
Let's go all together and tag someone.
RED TEAM WILL MOVE AS ONE AGAIN
-[Pani Bottle] They're hiding too.
-I'll go along.
Four of us will stick together,
and I'll try to tag them.
If we fail, just tag anyone.
-Me?
-Yeah, if it falls through.
[Pani Bottle] Should I put down
an 8 to check?
Use the 8 on Jaegyun.
[host] The Battle Round has begun.
[Joonsu] Four over here!
SPOTS RED TEAM ON OTHER SIDE
Is Pani Bottle here?
Get ready to tag!
Pani Bottle is coming!
Jaegyun's over there.
-[Ddolddol] Where?
-[Junseo] On the right.
-Horseking is in the middle.
-[Ddolddol] Okay.
[ZZONE] This is so scary.
-[Ddolddol] Who should go first?
-[Junseo] I'll go first.
-If I fail, just tag anyone.
-[Ddolddol] Okay.
-[Junseo] You can tag either of them.
RED TEAM'S TARGET: JAEGYUN, HORSEKING
[Junseo] First, we moved
as a group of four as we planned.
[Horseking] Be careful!
ZZONE, move out of the way.
Pani Bottle is running!
[Junseo] Once things get chaotic,
get behind them and strike.
RED TEAM MAKES THEIR MOVE
[Horseking] Junseo's coming for me.
[Junseo] I was targeting
Horseking and Jaegyun.
-Then, Jaegyun protected him from me.
-[Jaegyun exclaims]
YUK JUNSEO TAGS HWANG JAEGYUN
[alarm blaring]
[host] Tag confirmed.
-[Horseking] Junseo should be the King.
-[Jaegyun] What?
[Horseking] Junseo is the King.
Is this right?
[sighs] I think you should've ran
straight for Pani Bottle.
-That notebook's 100% legit.
-[Ddolddol] Yes.
[Pani Bottle] Horseking didn't tag me.
[Ddolddol] He could have,
but he didn't chase me.
Because it's a waste.
DESPERATELY AVOIDING JUNSEO
[Jimin] And since you have a 2,
he definitely assumes
your other card is high.
[Pani Bottle] I kept
thinking it over like hell.
[Jimin] You did amazing.
So the notebook was legit.
Horseking became more passive
and didn't tag Pani Bottle.
Jaegyun actively protected Horseking.
Jaegyun has to be the King.
CONVINCED JAEGYUN IS KING
By the way,
Jaegyun's got either a King or 6.
-Could he pull out a 6?
-Beats me.
He could played a 6.
If he believed Junseo was the King,
he can't play his King.
Then, he gets exposed as the King.
Then, he might play the 6.
-But if he does, thank you.
-[Ddolddol] Thank you so much.
We just need to catch
and eliminate Hwang Jaegyun.
[dealer] We will announce the results.
HWANG JAEGYUN VS. YUK JUNSEO
Yuk Junseo has won.
Mr. Yuk Junseo,
please come and take the card.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[sighs]
[Ddolddol] I wonder how it turned out.
What did you play?
I played an 8.
-[Pani Bottle] An 8?
-Jaegyun played a 7.
What?
-Jaegyun played...
-[Pani Bottle] An 8 and 7?
-...a 7?
-[Junseo] Yes.
So the notebook was wrong.
JAEGYUN: KING, 6
[Ddolddol] Wait,
we need an emergency meeting.
My mind seriously went blank. [chuckles]
Junseo played an 8
and claimed Jaegyun's 7.
The notebook said Jaegyun had
a King and 6, but he played a 7?
JAEGYUN: KING, 6
RED TEAM IN CONFUSION
So, this is wrong?
But I don't think it's a lot different
from this, don't you think?
I do think Jaegyun is the King.
But think about it.
If I were the King and had a 7,
would I play the 7 first?
I'd be completely vulnerable.
I'd just play a regular card.
Especially with everyone suspecting
Junseo as the King,
if I put down the King
and nothing happens,
then the game's over.
JIMIN THINKS IT'LL BE SIMILAR
But this might be fake.
I'm afraid we're relying too much on this.
Should I check Horseking?
Horseking does keep running away.
Ddolddol can step up...
Who do I need to avoid going up against?
-Just not against Jaegyun.
-[Ddolddol] Right?
[Junseo] Ddolddol,
want to eliminate Horseking?
Okay.
DDOLDDOL WILL ELIMINATE HORSEKING
[ZZONE] We've found
only one symbol, right?
-[Jaegyun] Yes.
-[ZZONE sighs]
I can't find any.
[ZZONE] Right?
We can't find anything in the reeds.
[Dail] We need to find symbols.
We need to keep going to the Reed Field.
Once it's dark,
we can't find any in the reeds.
If you can avoid getting caught
until I make my move,
I'll try to get one.
Let's try to find four first.
BLUE TEAM'S GOAL: FIND SYMBOLS
-[host] The Battle Round has begun.
-[alarm blaring]
[Ddolddol] That one?
[Jimin] Let's go!
[Pani Bottle] This way.
-[Pani Bottle] To the left.
-[Ddolddol] Left?
-[Pani Bottle] Yes, left.
-[Ddolddol] Okay, let's go to the left.
They're all coming!
They're all here!
EXCEPT FOR EUNSIL,
RED TEAM HEADS TO THE OTHER BASE
[Horseking] I'll go around.
Keep an eye on it.
Those four came back without Eunsil,
as if they were out taking a stroll.
I just need to find a symbol,
so let's focus on that.
[♪ exciting music playing]
[Joonsu] Where could it be?
[ZZONE] It's so hard to find them.
[Jimin] Where are they?
[Pani Bottle] They're searching
over there.
Right. I saw ZZONE.
[Jimin] Why are they searching so hard?
He checks that over and over again.
Nothing was there earlier, so why?
-[Ddolddol] Should we follow Dail?
-[Jimin] Dail's running like crazy.
I need to catch Horseking.
RED TEAM BASE
[Horseking] There was no one
in the opposing team's base.
[Junseo] Let's go search
since no one's here.
[Ddolddol] Okay.
ENTIRE RED TEAM EXCEPT EUNSIL
IS OUTSIDE
[panting]
[Horseking] I looked
around the second floor...
and found it right away.
[♪ exciting music playing]
[Jimin] Horseking!
SPOTS HORSEKING
WHO HAS FOUND A SYMBOL
[Ddolddol] Horseking is here!
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
There he was.
Horseking was right in front of me.
[Junseo] Catch them!
FAILS TO TAG
[Horseking] In that moment, I knew
I couldn't let myself get caught.
I thought,
"Run like your life depends on it."
JUNSEO HEADS THE OTHER WAY
HORSEKING ENTERS THE BASE
PANI BOTTLE SHOWS UP
[Pani Bottle] I dropped it.
FAILS TO TAG
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Horseking] It's over.
-I'm here.
-[Junseo] You didn't break it yet.
No, I have to give this to them to check.
[host] Tagging isn't allowed
in the Dealer Room.
[Horseking] You can't in here.
THE TARGET NARROWLY ESCAPED
BLUE TEAM DESTROYS SECOND SYMBOL
[panting]
[Junseo] I couldn't get him.
-[Ddolddol] What?
-[Junseo] I couldn't get him.
He was seriously fast. Why is he so fast?
I thought he was a cheetah.
[Horseking panting heavily]
[Horseking] What on earth?
[Ddolddol] Did you break it? [groans]
THE KING IS CONSIDERING TAGGING
HORSEKING TURNS AND COMES BACK
KIM DDOLDDOL TAGS HORSEKING
Let's go.
[host] Tag confirmed.
I really wanted to check Horseking.
It was obvious he had a high card.
If I was the King
and went up against a high card,
there was a risk of getting exposed.
But I wanted to use this chance
to figure out Horseking's rank.
This is Horseking.
KIM DDOLDDOL SUBMITS THE KING CARD
[dealer] We will announce the results.
[Pani Bottle] I think
we have the advantage now.
We have a huge advantage.
And we took out a strong card.
-[Pani Bottle] Yes, the 7 is gone.
-That's crazy good.
[ZZONE] They got that annoying Ddolddol.
[Jaegyun] But we don't know
what Ddolddol has.
[ZZONE exhales sharply]
[Horseking exhales sharply]
[Joonsu] Who won?
[Horseking] What?
[exhales] I can't run anymore.
[Ddolddol] This is an emergency.
[dealer] We will check both of your cards.
KIM DDOLDDOL: KING
HORSEKING: KING
[dealer] We will announce the results.
It's a tie.
Please take your cards.
KIM DDOLDDOL AND HORSEKING TIE
At that point, I thought, "I'm screwed."
I went in just to tag someone.
But of all people,
I ended up tagging the King.
How did I not see this coming?
He's Horseking. It's right in his name.
Why did I tag the King? I was so stupid.
[in English] Horseking.
[in Korean] K for "King."
[Ddolddol] Horseking and I
are both Kings. [sighs]
We were completely off.
[Pani Bottle] Hmm?
He's the King?
[Ddolddol] We both confirmed
we're the Kings.
-[Jimin] Nothing happened?
-Nope.
-Can we check out Joonsu's?
-[Ddolddol] Where's his notebook?
I think he changed it on purpose.
THE NOTEBOOK SAID JAEGYUN WAS KING
The King turned out to be him.
HORSEKING: 9, 1
JAEGYUN: KING, 6
It's not right, is it?
[Ddolddol] It's not right.
It's way different, right?
-It's a lie. It's fake.
-[♪ suspicious music playing]
Jimin still thought
it could be real until the end.
But it was just fake.
Things didn't add up.
Joonsu is capable of coming up
with a strategy like that?
[Horseking] Jimin clearly
and urgently shouted,
"Get Horseking!"
-[Jaegyun] Really?
-[ZZONE] Yes.
-She's certain it's me.
-[ZZONE] Right. Yeah.
[Jaegyun] So they took the notebook.
-[Joonsu] They bought it.
-[Horseking] They took it.
That was Blue Team's strategy.
1 HOUR AGO
[Jaegyun] Don't lose your notebook
after you write down the numbers.
[both laugh]
What if we use this against them?
[Jaegyun] Oh.
[both laughing]
We could write, "Horseking is 1 and 9,"
in the notebook and let them find it.
[Jaegyun] Shall we?
[whispers] I bet they'd fall for it.
This should be a lot of fun.
Make it look legit
with patterns like "1, 9."
MAKING A FAKE RANK CHART
Or like "Yang Dail, 2, 8."
[Joonsu] If they take the bait,
it'll be awesome.
It probably says Jaegyun was the King,
instead of Horseking.
In Round 1, all five of them
came along by the reeds.
That's when I went
into the alley on the right
and dropped the notebook
where it would look natural.
When I went back the following round,
it was gone.
AFTER ROUND 1
Hey.
They took my notebook.
-[Jaegyun] They took it?
-[Joonsu] Yes.
-Who? Really?
-[Joonsu] Yes, they took it.
[both laughing]
-They took it?
-[Joonsu] Yes, they did.
[ZZONE laughs]
[Joonsu] This is perfect.
[groans] I'm so pissed off.
[sighs] I was tricked by Joonsu?
I didn't want to believe it.
[Ddolddol] I think we should probably
stop checking this.
[Pani Bottle] Right, put it away.
Then, the chances of ZZONE
not being the Joker are really high.
I don't think ZZONE is the Joker.
They know we'd obviously think
it was ZZONE.
[Ddolddol] Then, who received the Joker?
[Jaegyun] Both teams
have confirmed who the King is.
[Horseking] Now,
it's about identifying the Joker.
[Jaegyun] Yes.
I'm convinced the Joker
is either Junseo or Eunsil.
I think it's probably one of them.
Giving the Joker to Junseo...
I think the Joker is definitely Eunsil,
-if you ask me.
-Because she's in hiding?
She's absent.
EUNSIL HAS BEEN HIDING
THE WHOLE TIME AND IS THE JOKER?
Yeah, to be honest,
if Eunsil is the Joker,
-I win.
-[Dail] Yeah.
No, she has one more.
-Right, the Joker has three cards.
-[Joonsu] Exactly.
THE PLAYER WITH THE JOKER CARD
HAS THREE CARDS
If she had one more card,
why would she play so passively?
That could be part of their act.
-The more we think about it...
-[Horseking] I know.
...we keep thinking about it.
[Jaegyun] We should
take them out one at a time.
Let's do that.
[Jaegyun] Then first,
let's get rid of Eunsil.
-[Horseking] We have to.
-[alarm blaring]
Let's go, let's go.
[♪ thrilling music playing]
-[ZZONE] Then I'll search.
-[Joonsu] I'll search too.
[host] The Battle Round has begun.
How is she hiding so well?
BLUE TEAM IS OFF TO CATCH EUNSIL
JANG EUNSIL IS HIDING IN THE SAME SPOT
ON THE SECOND FLOOR OF RED TEAM BASE
This was the base.
[Dail] I'll go this way.
Okay, can you go over there?
PANI BOTTLE WAS IN RED TEAM BASE
[♪ tense music playing]
Yang Dail?
[Pani Bottle exclaims]
That was a close one.
HORSEKING IS ONE STEP LATE
Horseking's that way.
Horseking's at our base.
[Junseo] Okay.
[Pani Bottle] Horseking's at our base.
[Jimin] He said Horseking's at our base.
[Pani Bottle] Horseking's behind you.
Over there.
You have to protect us.
[Jimin] Sure, block Horseking.
[Ddolddol] I'll stay on Horseking.
DDOLDDOL IS TRYING
TO PROTECT HIS TEAMMATES
[Horseking] Where's Eunsil hiding?
HORSEKING'S SUDDEN CHARGE
DODGES DDOLDDOL AND TAGS JIMIN
HORSEKING TAGS PARK JIMIN
-[host] Tag confirmed.
-[Ddolddol] So tough.
[Horseking] Our plan
is to take away their cards
and make them more passive.
[Jimin panting heavily]
[Horseking] Where is Eunsil?
You're not going to play
the King card, right?
[Horseking] Sorry?
[Jimin] He's not going to use
the King, right?
Would he play the King right away?
[Junseo] Now that
the King's been revealed,
there's no reason not to play it.
[groans] Please, use the Joker.
[Ddolddol] The Joker needs to act
when running and tagging.
BEFORE START OF GAME
Then, I'll give you
the Joker to start with.
-Okay.
-[Ddolddol] Because you're good
at keeping a poker face.
-[Pani Bottle] Jimin will take care of it.
-[Ddolddol] Yes.
[Jimin] I managed to get the Joker.
THE BATTLE BETWEEN HORSEKING AND JIMIN
[♪ suspenseful string music playing]
[scoffs] Seriously.
[Jimin] If Horseking plays the King
and I play the Joker,
that would end the game
after only 30 minutes.
But I think I was unsure
because Horseking had a regular card.
JOKER LOSES TO ALL CARDS EXCEPT KING
[exhales deeply]
[dealer] Mr. Horseking
has submitted his card.
[Jimin] He wouldn't play the King, right?
HORSEKING SUBMITS THE KING
[Horseking] This is all about momentum.
We need to show
our team's strength from the start.
[Jimin] Should I play the Joker?
Should I really play it?
[dealer] Ms. Park Jimin
has submitted her card.
He wouldn't play the King, right?
[♪ music crescendos]
[♪ music fades]
[dealer] We will announce the results.
[♪ music continues]
[♪ ominous music playing]
Translated by Youji Kim